<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Intro to the workshop on Nginx Experience</title><link>http://example.org/010_intro/</link><description>Recent content in Intro to the workshop on Nginx Experience</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 14:11:17 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/010_intro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AWS Workshop Portal</title><link>http://example.org/010_intro/010_aws_wokshop_portal_1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 14:37:59 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/010_intro/010_aws_wokshop_portal_1/</guid><description>This workshop creates an AWS account and a Cloud9 environment. You will need the Participant Hash provided upon entry, and your email address to track your unique session.
Connect to the portal by clicking the button or browsing to https://dashboard.eventengine.run/. The following screen shows up. Enter the provided hash in the text box. The button on the bottom right corner changes to Accept Terms &amp;amp; Login. Click on that button to continue.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Formation</title><link>http://example.org/010_intro/020_cloudformation_1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 14:37:59 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/010_intro/020_cloudformation_1/</guid><description>Click the bellow button and deploy the template:
Click Next 3 times accepting all the defaults, but make sure the following is selected on the last screen: Click Create stack. Wait until the NGINX-EKS stack Status is CREATE_COMPLETE.</description></item><item><title>IAM Role</title><link>http://example.org/010_intro/030_iam_role_1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 14:37:59 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/010_intro/030_iam_role_1/</guid><description> Follow this deep link to find your Cloud9 EC2 instance
Select the instance, then choose Actions / Instance Settings / Attach/Replace IAM Role
Choose eksworkshop-admin from the IAM Role drop down, and select Apply</description></item><item><title>Cloud 9</title><link>http://example.org/010_intro/040_cloud9_1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 14:37:59 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/010_intro/040_cloud9_1/</guid><description>Open the Cloud9 console, and click on Open IDE. This will open a cloud-based integrated development environment (IDE) that lets you write, run, and debug your code with just a browser. It includes a code editor, debugger, and a terminal. We will be using it for the rest of the workshop.
Ad blockers, javascript disablers, and tracking blockers should be disabled for the cloud9 domain, or connecting to the workspace might be impacted.</description></item></channel></rss>